formice.com 2016-06-23

# Cheeseformice: Speak the Cheese!

### Privacy Policy/Terms of Service

The following page outlines how Cheeseformice uses and protects the personal information of its users.

**Information Collected**

When visiting Cheeseformice, any of the following information may be collected for statistical and/or debugging purposes: Internet Protocol (IP) address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system and version, referral source, length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity.

**Disclosure of Information**

Cheeseformice values the privacy of its users and will never share, sell, rent, or otherwise disclose any personal information unless we have your explicit permission or when required to comply with legal or regulatory provisions.

**Cookies**

Cheeseformice uses a small string of text called a cookie to store information on your browser upon your first visit. This information may include your preferences and session identification. The main function of cookies on Cheeseformice is to allow you to return to the site without requiring a log in every time.

We also use third party advertisements on Cheeseformice to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they display advertisements which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites you have visited.

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

Google may use DoubleClick DART cookies for ad serving through its Adsense network and other affiliates, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising. This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest-based advertising"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART uses non-personally identifiable information. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/#toc-optout)

**Limitation of Liability**

IN NO EVENT SHALL CHEESEFORMICE, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, OR VOLUNTEERS BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM YOUR USAGE OF CHEESEFORMICE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO ERRORS, MISTAKES, INACCURACIES, OR OMISSIONS OF CONTENT, PERSONAL OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USAGE OF OUR SERVERS AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION STORED THEREIN, OR ANY BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES OR THE LIKE WHICH MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH OUR WEBSITE OR BY ANY THIRD PARTY SERVICE USED BY CHEESEFORMICE.

**Website Policy Changes**

Cheeseformice reserves the right to change this, and any other policy located on our website at any time without notifying our users.

**Agreement**

By using and/or visiting this website, you are agreeing to the terms and policies enumerated on this page. If you do not agree to any of these terms or policies, do not use our website.
